[{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79340"},"order":1,"name":"Hometown","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"20.04.2024","questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79341"},"order":1,"question":"Please describe your hometown a little.","answer":"My hometown is a picturesque suburban area nestled between rolling hills and lush greenery. It exudes a serene charm with its quaint streets lined with cozy houses and vibrant gardens. The community is tight-knit, with friendly neighbors always ready to lend a helping hand. The centerpiece of the town is its historic main street, adorned with charming boutiques, cafes, and local businesses. Surrounded by nature reserves and scenic trails, outdoor enthusiasts have ample opportunities for hiking, biking, and exploring the natural beauty of the area. Overall, it's a peaceful and idyllic place where residents take pride in their community and its rich history.","ideas":["sprawling industrial","dynamic","bustling","busy and fast-paced","ancient","old","modern"],"vocabulary":["within walking distance","within a short stroll","city life","city authorities","city facilities"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79342"},"order":2,"question":"What is your town well-known for?","answer":"My town is well-known for its historic landmarks, beautiful parks, and vibrant cultural scene. It's famous for its annual festivals, delicious cuisine, and friendly locals.","ideas":["historic landmarks","beautiful parks","vibrant cultural scene","annual festivals","delicious cuisine","friendly locals"],"vocabulary":["landmarks","festivals","cuisine","locals"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79343"},"order":3,"question":"Do you like your hometown?","answer":"Yes, I love my hometown. It holds a special place in my heart because of its charm, community spirit, and natural beauty.","ideas":["community spirit","natural beauty"],"vocabulary":["charm","special place"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79344"},"order":4,"question":"Is that a big city or a small place?","answer":"It's a small town with a cozy atmosphere and a strong sense of community.","ideas":["cozy atmosphere","strong sense of community"],"vocabulary":["small town","atmosphere","community"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79345"},"order":5,"question":"How long have you been living there?","answer":"I've been living in my hometown for about 10 years now. It's been a wonderful experience, and I've grown to love this place.","ideas":["wonderful experience","grown to love"],"vocabulary":["living","experience","grown","love"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79346"},"order":6,"question":"Do you think you will continue living there for a long time?","answer":"Yes, I plan to stay here for the foreseeable future. I feel deeply connected to this town and can't imagine living anywhere else.","ideas":["plan to stay","foreseeable future","deeply connected","imagine living"],"vocabulary":["foreseeable future","connected","imagine"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79347"},"order":7,"question":"Would you like to live in the countryside in the future?","answer":"While I appreciate the tranquility and simplicity of countryside living, I'm quite attached to my hometown. However, I wouldn't rule out the possibility of living in the countryside someday.","ideas":["tranquility","simplicity","attached to","wouldn't rule out","someday"],"vocabulary":["countryside living","tranquility","simplicity","attached","possibility","someday"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79348"},"order":8,"question":"Have you ever lived in the countryside?","answer":"No, I've never lived in the countryside, but I've visited rural areas and enjoyed the peaceful surroundings.","ideas":["visited rural areas","enjoyed peaceful surroundings"],"vocabulary":["countryside","rural areas","peaceful surroundings"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79349"},"order":9,"question":"Do you ever spend time in the countryside?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy spending time in the countryside, especially during weekends or holidays. It's refreshing to escape the hustle and bustle of the city and reconnect with nature.","ideas":["enjoy spending time","especially during weekends or holidays","refreshing","escape the hustle and bustle","reconnect with nature"],"vocabulary":["countryside","weekends","holidays","refreshing","escape","reconnect with nature"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79350"},"order":10,"question":"What is the difference between living in the countryside and the city?","answer":"Living in the countryside offers a quieter and more relaxed lifestyle, closer to nature. In contrast, city living is often faster-paced and offers more amenities and opportunities.","ideas":["quieter and more relaxed lifestyle","closer to nature","faster-paced","more amenities and opportunities"],"vocabulary":["countryside living","quieter","relaxed lifestyle","nature","faster-paced","amenities","opportunities"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79351"},"order":11,"question":"What do people living in the countryside like to do?","answer":"People living in the countryside often enjoy outdoor activities such as hiking, gardening, and fishing. They also value community events and gatherings.","ideas":["enjoy outdoor activities","hiking","gardening","fishing","value community events","gatherings"],"vocabulary":["countryside","outdoor activities","hiking","gardening","fishing","community events","gatherings"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79352"},"order":12,"question":"What do you like to do in the countryside?","answer":"I love exploring nature trails, having picnics in scenic spots, and enjoying the peace and quiet. It's a great way to unwind and recharge.","ideas":["love exploring nature trails","having picnics in scenic spots","enjoying the peace and quiet","unwind and recharge"],"vocabulary":["countryside","nature trails","picnics","scenic spots","peace and quiet","unwind","recharge"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79353"},"order":13,"question":"How has your town changed over the last 20 years?","answer":"Over the last 20 years, my town has undergone significant development and modernization. New infrastructure projects, improved transportation, and urban renewal initiatives have transformed the landscape. However, there has also been a growing concern about preserving the town's historic character amidst rapid urbanization.","ideas":["undergone significant development","modernization","new infrastructure projects","improved transportation","urban renewal initiatives","transformed the landscape","growing concern about preserving the town's historic character","rapid urbanization"],"vocabulary":["significant development","modernization","infrastructure projects","transportation","urban renewal","landscape","preserving historic character","urbanization"]}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"662f6dc8b9d737bcb86a5d4c"},"order":2,"name":"Home decoration","questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"662f6dc8b9d737bcb86a5d4d"},"order":1,"question":"What color would you choose to paint the walls of your room?","answer":"I'd choose sky blue for my room's walls. It brings a sense of calmness and elegance, expands the space visually, and pairs well with various decor styles. Plus, it brightens the room and creates a soothing atmosphere for relaxation.","vocabulary":["to look homey","to start home improvements","to add homey touches","living space"],"ideas":["have it refurbished","breathe more life into by","induce some color into my flat","add warmth"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"662f6dc8b9d737bcb86a5d4e"},"order":2,"question":"What color would you never use in your home?","answer":"I'd avoid using dark colors like black or deep red because they tend to make spaces feel smaller and more confined. Instead, I prefer lighter, more neutral tones that create an open and airy atmosphere.","vocabulary":["dark colors","to make spaces feel smaller","more neutral tones","open and airy atmosphere"],"ideas":["opt for lighter shades","choose neutral color palettes","incorporate natural light","use mirrors to reflect light"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"662f6dc8b9d737bcb86a5d4f"},"order":3,"question":"Can you describe the place where you live?","answer":"I live in a vibrant urban neighborhood nestled amidst towering skyscrapers and bustling streets. The area is teeming with life, with colorful markets, cozy cafes, and diverse cultural landmarks around every corner. The architecture is a mix of modern high-rises and quaint historic buildings, creating a unique blend of old and new. Parks and green spaces provide a refreshing retreat from the urban hustle, offering opportunities for leisurely strolls and relaxation. Overall, it's a dynamic and lively place that never fails to inspire and captivate.","vocabulary":["vibrant urban neighborhood","towering skyscrapers","bustling streets","quaint historic buildings"],"ideas":["explore local markets","discover hidden cafes","visit cultural landmarks","enjoy leisurely strolls in parks"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"662f6dc8b9d737bcb86a5d50"},"order":4,"question":"What kind of housing accommodation do you live in?","answer":"I live in a cozy apartment located in the heart of the city. It's a modern building with all the necessary amenities, including a gym, swimming pool, and 24/7 security. The apartment itself is spacious and well-designed, with large windows that let in plenty of natural light. Overall, it's the perfect blend of comfort and convenience.","vocabulary":["cozy apartment","modern building","necessary amenities","spacious and well-designed"],"ideas":["decorate with modern furniture","optimize storage space","create a cozy ambiance","personalize with decorative accents"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"662f6dc8b9d737bcb86a5d51"},"order":5,"question":"What do you like about your flat?","answer":"One thing I really like about my flat is its stunning view of the city skyline. It's especially breathtaking at night when all the lights are twinkling. I also appreciate the spacious layout and the abundance of natural light that floods the space during the day. Overall, it's a comfortable and inviting place to call home.","vocabulary":["stunning view","city skyline","breathtaking at night","abundance of natural light"],"ideas":["create a cozy reading nook by the window","add indoor plants to bring in greenery","hang sheer curtains to soften the sunlight","install smart lighting for ambiance"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"662f6dc8b9d737bcb86a5d52"},"order":6,"question":"Which room does your family spend most of the time in?","answer":"We tend to spend most of our time in the living room, as it's the heart of our home. It's where we gather to relax, watch TV, and spend quality time together as a family. The comfortable seating, warm lighting, and cozy ambiance make it the perfect place to unwind after a long day.","vocabulary":["heart of our home","gather to relax","spend quality time together","cozy ambiance"],"ideas":["create a cozy seating area with plush sofas","add a coffee table for snacks and drinks","install a TV for entertainment","decorate with family photos and artwork"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"662f6dc8b9d737bcb86a5d53"},"order":7,"question":"What can you see from the window where you live?","answer":"From my window, I have a picturesque view of the city skyline, with towering skyscrapers and twinkling lights stretching out into the distance. On clear days, I can even see the mountains in the distance, adding to the scenic beauty of the landscape.","vocabulary":["picturesque view","city skyline","twinkling lights","scenic beauty"],"ideas":["create a cozy window seat to enjoy the view","hang sheer curtains to frame the scenery","install window boxes for potted plants","place decorative accents on the windowsill"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"662f6dc8b9d737bcb86a5d54"},"order":8,"question":"Do you prefer living in a house or a flat?","answer":"I prefer living in a flat because of the convenience and amenities it offers. In a flat, everything is within easy reach, from shops and restaurants to public transportation and entertainment venues. Plus, most flats come with modern amenities like gyms, swimming pools, and security systems, making them a comfortable and convenient choice for urban living.","vocabulary":["convenience and amenities","within easy reach","modern amenities","comfortable and convenient choice"],"ideas":["explore nearby shops and restaurants","take advantage of public transportation","enjoy the amenities offered by the building","connect with neighbors in the communal spaces"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"662f6dc8b9d737bcb86a5d55"},"order":9,"question":"What would you like to change in your flat?","answer":"If I could change one thing about my flat, it would be the lack of outdoor space. While I love the convenience and amenities of urban living, I miss having a private garden or balcony where I can relax and enjoy the outdoors. In the future, I'd love to find a flat with a small outdoor space where I can grow plants and soak up the sun.","vocabulary":["lack of outdoor space","private garden","balcony","soak up the sun"],"ideas":["look for flats with balconies or terraces","create an indoor garden with potted plants","hang window boxes for herbs and flowers","invest in a rooftop garden membership"]},{"_id":{"$oid":"662f6dc8b9d737bcb86a5d56"},"order":10,"question":"What do you dislike about your flat?","answer":"One thing I dislike about my flat is the noise from the street below. Since I live in a busy urban area, there's always traffic noise and city sounds filtering into the apartment, especially during rush hour. It can be distracting at times, especially when I'm trying to relax or focus on work.","vocabulary":["noise from the street below","traffic noise","city sounds","distracting at times"],"ideas":["invest in soundproofing materials for the windows","use rugs and curtains to absorb sound","create a designated quiet area in the flat","wear noise-canceling headphones when needed"]}],"author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"29.04.2024"},{"_id":{"$oid":"6639abcc5ab08aa66684208e"},"name":"Work and Studies","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"07.05.2024","questions":[{"question":"Do you work or are you a student?","answer":"I work as a software engineer.","vocabulary":["employment","occupation","profession","academic pursuits"],"ideas":["career development","educational goals"],"_id":{"$oid":"4aa212624b3a7eb4564e6db2"},"order":1},{"question":"What work do you do? What subjects are you studying?","answer":"I work as a software engineer, specializing in web development. I'm also studying computer science at university, focusing on algorithms and data structures.","vocabulary":["job role","field of study","academic disciplines","curriculum"],"ideas":["career aspirations","educational interests"],"_id":{"$oid":"c751cadb32a6b7687a7a9899"},"order":2},{"question":"Why did you choose that job? Why did you choose that subject?","answer":"I chose to work as a software engineer because I've always been passionate about technology and enjoy problem-solving. Similarly, I chose to study computer science because I find the field fascinating and see a lot of potential for growth and innovation.","vocabulary":["motivation","reasoning","interests","career prospects"],"ideas":["personal goals","academic motivations"],"_id":{"$oid":"0a67b61d2e5078ce56b7083d"},"order":3},{"question":"Do you like your job?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy my job as a software engineer. I find it challenging and rewarding.","vocabulary":["job satisfaction","career fulfillment","work enjoyment"],"ideas":["professional contentment","workplace experiences"],"_id":{"$oid":"cc4df3868bf90d9eca8e0e5f"},"order":4},{"question":"Is there anything you dislike about your job?","answer":"While I enjoy my job overall, there are occasional stressful deadlines and challenges that can be difficult to navigate.","vocabulary":["job challenges","workplace frustrations","career obstacles"],"ideas":["workplace stressors","job-related difficulties"],"_id":{"$oid":"1d8beadd86685a4ba98864aa"},"order":5},{"question":"What do you like about your studies?","answer":"I appreciate the opportunity to learn new concepts and expand my knowledge in the field of computer science. I also enjoy the collaborative nature of academic projects and discussions.","vocabulary":["academic benefits","learning opportunities","educational advantages"],"ideas":["academic interests","learning experiences"],"_id":{"$oid":"36db3a7ec6f910f5eb23ca94"},"order":6},{"question":"What do you dislike about your studies?","answer":"Sometimes, the workload can be overwhelming, especially during exam periods or when multiple assignments are due simultaneously.","vocabulary":["academic challenges","study frustrations","educational stressors"],"ideas":["academic pressures","study-related difficulties"],"_id":{"$oid":"5d24ad4a885bca022d21fd65"},"order":7},{"question":"What was your dream job when you were young?","answer":"When I was young, I dreamed of becoming an astronaut and exploring outer space.","vocabulary":["childhood aspirations","dream careers","future ambitions"],"ideas":["career dreams","aspirational goals"],"_id":{"$oid":"fdf7c4dfb91632458a4e0116"},"order":8},{"question":"Have you changed your mind on your dream job?","answer":"Yes, as I grew older and discovered new interests, my career aspirations evolved. While I still find space exploration fascinating, I've found my passion in technology and software development.","vocabulary":["career changes","revised ambitions","evolving goals"],"ideas":["career shifts","aspirational changes"],"_id":{"$oid":"9e7447ab87cea1c634cad1cc"},"order":9}],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"6639af865ab08aa66684208f"},"name":"Colors","questions":[{"question":"What color car would you choose to buy?","answer":"I would choose a sleek black car. Black cars often exude a sense of elegance and sophistication, and they tend to maintain their value well in the resale market.","ideas":["Consider factors like personal preference, resale value, and climate."],"vocabulary":["Preference","Resale value","Aesthetic"],"_id":{"$oid":"56575a4391f4c3ce56e59ce2"},"order":1},{"question":"What is your favorite color?","answer":"My favorite color is blue. I find it calming and serene, and it reminds me of clear skies and peaceful waters.","ideas":["Discuss personal preference, emotional connection, and symbolism."],"vocabulary":["Preference","Emotion","Symbolism"],"_id":{"$oid":"302b21cd5df2a14408af01e3"},"order":2},{"question":"What is the most popular color in your country?","answer":"In my country, blue is often considered the most popular color. It symbolizes trust, reliability, and stability, which are highly valued traits.","ideas":["Consider cultural influences, trends, and societal preferences."],"vocabulary":["Culture","Trend","Preference"],"_id":{"$oid":"2cfdade92c862656093e9572"},"order":3},{"question":"Do you think colors influence you?","answer":"Absolutely, colors have a significant influence on me. For example, warm tones like red can evoke feelings of passion and energy, while cool tones like green can promote a sense of relaxation and harmony.","ideas":["Explore the psychological impact of colors on mood and behavior."],"vocabulary":["Influence","Psychology","Mood"],"_id":{"$oid":"2bc04efe85f251801c98c23c"},"order":4},{"question":"Do you think colors are important?","answer":"Yes, colors are incredibly important. They play a crucial role in communication, evoke emotions, and can even influence decision-making. In design and branding, colors can convey messages and create memorable experiences.","ideas":["Discuss the role of colors in communication and branding."],"vocabulary":["Importance","Communication","Branding"],"_id":{"$oid":"afbb51d3d2338fd48b0624ed"},"order":5},{"question":"Were colors important to you when you were a child?","answer":"Yes, colors were very important to me. For example, I had a favorite toy that was brightly colored, and I always enjoyed drawing with vibrant crayons.","ideas":["Reflect on childhood memories and favorite toys."],"vocabulary":["Childhood","Memories","Imagination"],"_id":{"$oid":"b3a0e9515abf598a9b00ba16"},"order":6}],"author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"07.05.2024","order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"6639b1d05ab08aa666842090"},"name":"Cake","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"07.05.2024","questions":[{"question":"Have you ever made a cake yourself?","answer":"","ideas":["Try baking a cake at home","Experiment with different cake recipes","Join a baking class to learn how to make cakes"],"vocabulary":["bake","recipe","icing","frosting","oven","mixer","batter","flour","sugar","eggs"],"_id":{"$oid":"34f8d5b0ca92293ce74e8afa"},"order":1},{"question":"Do you like cakes?","answer":"","ideas":["Try different types of cakes to discover your favorite","Bake a cake as a special treat for yourself","Visit a bakery to explore various cake options"],"vocabulary":["delicious","sweet","flavorful","moist","decadent","spongy","icing","frosting","layered","celebratory"],"_id":{"$oid":"f14a00986c29457bcd26ef67"},"order":2},{"question":"Did you like cakes when you were a child?","answer":"","ideas":["Reflect on your favorite childhood cake memories","Recreate a favorite childhood cake recipe","Share childhood cake stories with friends or family"],"vocabulary":["nostalgic","childhood memories","sweet tooth","birthday cakes","special occasions"],"_id":{"$oid":"8e1de577d9261b158f9e7e2f"},"order":3},{"question":"Do you eat cakes or other sweet things after a meal?","answer":"","ideas":["Explore different dessert options","Experiment with healthier dessert alternatives","Learn to balance indulgence with moderation"],"vocabulary":["dessert","sweet treat","indulgence","moderation","sugar rush","cravings","guilty pleasure"],"_id":{"$oid":"cd27dec2f82713bcafdf9934"},"order":4}],"order":5},{"_id":{"$oid":"6639b3995ab08aa666842092"},"name":"Sunglasses","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"07.05.2024","questions":[{"question":"Do you wear sunglasses?","answer":"Yes, I wear sunglasses regularly, especially when I'm outdoors on sunny days.","ideas":["regularly","outdoors","sunny days"],"vocabulary":["sunglasses","regularly","outdoors","sunny days"],"_id":{"$oid":"decec1c95679354b6a34ecdb"},"order":1},{"question":"Why do you wear sunglasses?","answer":"I wear sunglasses to protect my eyes from harmful UV rays and to reduce glare, which helps me see more comfortably in bright sunlight.","ideas":["protect eyes from harmful UV rays","reduce glare","see more comfortably","bright sunlight"],"vocabulary":["sunglasses","protect","UV rays","reduce glare","comfortably","bright sunlight"],"_id":{"$oid":"bc927af28adfad10cf0b8363"},"order":2},{"question":"How often do you buy sunglasses?","answer":"I buy sunglasses occasionally, usually when my current pair gets damaged or lost, or if I want to update my style.","ideas":["occasionally","current pair gets damaged or lost","update my style"],"vocabulary":["sunglasses","occasionally","damaged","lost","update style"],"_id":{"$oid":"23c6157f56786ec27eefb37d"},"order":3},{"question":"Have you ever lost your sunglasses?","answer":"Yes, I've lost my sunglasses a couple of times, which can be frustrating, but it's also a good reminder to be more careful with them.","ideas":["lost sunglasses","frustrating","be more careful"],"vocabulary":["sunglasses","lost","frustrating","careful"],"_id":{"$oid":"09fa6e3d96ad61d8c630a4d2"},"order":4}],"order":6},{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79342"},"name":"Social Media","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"07.05.2024","questions":[{"question":"Do you like social media?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy using social media platforms to stay connected with friends and family, as well as to discover interesting content.","ideas":["stay connected with friends and family","discover interesting content"],"vocabulary":["social media","enjoy","stay connected","friends and family","discover","interesting content"],"_id":{"$oid":"a0f2731f48721012b1e44c26"},"order":1},{"question":"Do your friends use social media?","answer":"Yes, most of my friends use social media to varying degrees. It's a common way for us to communicate and share updates.","ideas":["most of my friends use social media","varying degrees","common way to communicate","share updates"],"vocabulary":["friends","social media","communicate","share updates"],"_id":{"$oid":"111cc42fa4ea503944bca403"},"order":2},{"question":"What is the most popular social media platform in your country?","answer":"The most popular social media platform in my country is [Insert Platform Name], with a large user base and diverse features.","ideas":["most popular social media platform","large user base","diverse features"],"vocabulary":["popular","social media platform","user base","features"],"_id":{"$oid":"f43ad4aeca79fba4a20898dd"},"order":3},{"question":"What kind of people do you like to be friends with on those websites?","answer":"I like to be friends with people who share similar interests, values, and positive interactions on social media.","ideas":["similar interests","values","positive interactions"],"vocabulary":["friends","similar interests","values","positive interactions"],"_id":{"$oid":"ef4ade08974fd3740f5977ee"},"order":4},{"question":"What kind of social networking websites do you like to use?","answer":"I prefer social networking websites that offer a user-friendly interface, privacy features, and a diverse range of content.","ideas":["user-friendly interface","privacy features","diverse range of content"],"vocabulary":["social networking websites","user-friendly","privacy features","diverse range of content"],"_id":{"$oid":"6a24a12584406e906a6eac3a"},"order":5},{"question":"What kind of chatting apps or software do people in your country like to use?","answer":"People in my country commonly use messaging apps like [Insert Messaging App Name] and [Insert Messaging App Name] for instant communication and staying in touch.","ideas":["commonly use messaging apps","instant communication","staying in touch"],"vocabulary":["chatting apps","messaging apps","instant communication","staying in touch"],"_id":{"$oid":"4761938683eea7d7e2052cf8"},"order":6}],"order":7},{"_id":{"$oid":"660a8eafdef13c1c68a79343"},"name":"Music","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"07.05.2024","questions":[{"question":"What kind of music do you like to listen to?","answer":"I enjoy listening to a variety of genres, including pop, rock, classical, and electronic music. It depends on my mood and the situation.","ideas":["variety of genres","pop","rock","classical","electronic music","depends on mood and situation"],"vocabulary":["music","genres","pop","rock","classical","electronic","mood","situation"],"_id":{"$oid":"ebbb3dfe30c986d2e31b1e3b"},"order":1},{"question":"What kinds of music are the most popular in your country?","answer":"In my country, popular music genres include [Insert Genre], [Insert Genre], and [Insert Genre], with each having a significant following among listeners.","ideas":["popular music genres","significant following among listeners"],"vocabulary":["popular","music genres","following","listeners"],"_id":{"$oid":"aedebd537705727482b950b4"},"order":2},{"question":"Have you ever learned to play a musical instrument?","answer":"Yes, I have learned to play [Insert Instrument]. I find playing music to be a rewarding and enjoyable experience.","ideas":["learned to play a musical instrument","rewarding and enjoyable experience"],"vocabulary":["learned","musical instrument","rewarding","enjoyable"],"_id":{"$oid":"a6fc4c2a5475b683be6382ea"},"order":3},{"question":"Is music an important subject at schools in your country?","answer":"Yes, music is considered an important subject in schools in my country, as it helps students develop creativity, cultural appreciation, and teamwork skills.","ideas":["important subject","develop creativity","cultural appreciation","teamwork skills"],"vocabulary":["music","subject","creativity","cultural appreciation","teamwork"],"_id":{"$oid":"6e7dfddcae9b2e8323f110a4"},"order":4},{"question":"When did you start listening to that type of music?","answer":"I started listening to [Insert Genre/Type of Music] when I was [Insert Age], and it quickly became a favorite of mine.","ideas":["started listening to","became a favorite"],"vocabulary":["listening","genre","favorite"],"_id":{"$oid":"0d2dccfe105fa9397d1ab24e"},"order":5},{"question":"Do you often listen to music?","answer":"Yes, I listen to music regularly, especially during [Insert Time of Day] or when I'm [Insert Activity]. It's a great way to relax and unwind.","ideas":["regularly","especially during [Insert Time of Day]","when I'm [Insert Activity]","relax and unwind"],"vocabulary":["listen","regularly","time of day","activity","relax","unwind"],"_id":{"$oid":"623fd771bb6cbb71295cf252"},"order":6},{"question":"When do you listen to music?","answer":"I listen to music [Insert Frequency], particularly when I'm [Insert Activity] or [Insert Activity]. It helps me [Insert Purpose or Feeling].","ideas":["frequency","when I'm [Insert Activity]","when I'm [Insert Activity]","helps me [Insert Purpose or Feeling]"],"vocabulary":["listen","frequency","activity","purpose","feeling"],"_id":{"$oid":"a0a8f2069a9f86baf0d1f364"},"order":7},{"question":"How much time do you spend listening to music every day?","answer":"I typically spend around [Insert Time] listening to music each day, whether it's during my commute, work breaks, or leisure time.","ideas":["spend listening to music every day","during commute, work breaks, or leisure time"],"vocabulary":["time","listening to music","commute","work breaks","leisure time"],"_id":{"$oid":"7e6866ef5139a0baddce4c83"},"order":8},{"question":"How do you feel when you listen to music?","answer":"Listening to music makes me feel [Insert Emotion/Feeling], and it often has a [Insert Impact] on my mood.","ideas":["feel when listening to music","impact on mood"],"vocabulary":["listening","music","feel","emotion","impact","mood"],"_id":{"$oid":"9023df58da3269c84ae36c1c"},"order":9},{"question":"Do you like listening to songs?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy listening to songs, especially those with meaningful lyrics or catchy melodies.","ideas":["enjoy listening to songs","meaningful lyrics","catchy melodies"],"vocabulary":["listen","songs","meaningful","lyrics","catchy","melodies"],"_id":{"$oid":"585b1a3d69a9ddccc0a64b9a"},"order":10},{"question":"Have you ever been to a musical performance or concert?","answer":"Yes, I have attended several musical performances and concerts. It's always a thrilling experience to see artists perform live.","ideas":["attended musical performances or concerts","thrilling experience","see artists perform live"],"vocabulary":["musical performances","concerts","thrilling","experience","artists","perform live"],"_id":{"$oid":"3301aa91c21dace5452050a3"},"order":11},{"question":"Do you like listening to music at work?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy listening to music while I work. It helps me stay focused and motivated.","ideas":["enjoy listening to music at work","stay focused and motivated"],"vocabulary":["listen","music","work","stay focused","motivated"],"_id":{"$oid":"1fa0bf517ef3c328763865be"},"order":12},{"question":"Did you often listen to music when you were a child?","answer":"Yes, I used to listen to music frequently when I was a child. It played a significant role in my upbringing and entertainment.","ideas":["often listen to music when you were a child","played a significant role in upbringing and entertainment"],"vocabulary":["listen","music","child","role","upbringing","entertainment"],"_id":{"$oid":"f7fd7b48c506a46db3a74875"},"order":13},{"question":"Do people prefer to buy CDs or download music online?","answer":"In my country, people predominantly prefer to download music online due to its convenience and accessibility.","ideas":["prefer to buy CDs or download music online","convenience","accessibility"],"vocabulary":["buy","CDs","download","music","online","convenience","accessibility"],"_id":{"$oid":"0f22507f6c92f3e31d9c9efc"},"order":14}],"order":8},{"_id":{"$oid":"663ccbb4691ff22b0d1cc95b"},"name":"Collecting Things","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","questions":[{"question":"What items are considered collectibles in your country?","answer":"In my country, items such as stamps, coins, vintage toys, antique furniture, and rare books are commonly considered collectibles.","ideas":["stamps","coins","vintage toys","antique furniture","rare books"],"vocabulary":["collectibles","vintage","antique","rare"],"_id":{"$oid":"520a000f743728563bb92180"},"order":1},{"question":"Is collecting a popular pastime in your country?","answer":"Yes, collecting is a popular pastime in my country. Many people have diverse collections and participate in collectors' clubs and events.","ideas":["popular pastime","collectors' clubs","events"],"vocabulary":["pastime","collectors","participate","clubs","events"],"_id":{"$oid":"14d8e1beb4083e20faf29d2a"},"order":2},{"question":"Do a lot of people in your country collect things?","answer":"Yes, a significant number of people in my country are collectors. It's a hobby enjoyed by people of all ages and backgrounds.","ideas":["significant number","people of all ages and backgrounds"],"vocabulary":["collectors","hobby","enjoyed","ages","backgrounds"],"_id":{"$oid":"09d8461faa0af61ecd8e0e50"},"order":3},{"question":"Why do some people like collecting?","answer":"Some people enjoy collecting because it allows them to pursue their interests, preserve history, connect with others who share similar passions, and experience the thrill of finding rare or unique items.","ideas":["pursue their interests","preserve history","connect with others","share similar passions","experience the thrill","finding rare or unique items"],"vocabulary":["interests","preserve","connect","passions","thrill","unique items"],"_id":{"$oid":"691bf17b97547d47a850aa48"},"order":4},{"question":"What are the benefits of collecting?","answer":"Collecting can provide mental stimulation, relaxation, a sense of accomplishment, opportunities for social interaction, and potentially financial gains through the appreciation of valuable items.","ideas":["mental stimulation","relaxation","sense of accomplishment","social interaction","financial gains","appreciation of valuable items"],"vocabulary":["benefits","stimulation","accomplishment","interaction","financial gains","appreciation"],"_id":{"$oid":"e79c9f75b533484871ff5f18"},"order":5},{"question":"Do you collect things?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy collecting vintage records and rare coins. It's a hobby that brings me joy and allows me to learn about history and culture.","ideas":["enjoy collecting","vintage records","rare coins","brings joy","learn about history and culture"],"vocabulary":["vintage","rare","joy","history","culture"],"_id":{"$oid":"658d017ac41374cdf0399593"},"order":6}],"order":9},{"_id":{"$oid":"663ccd06691ff22b0d1cc95c"},"name":"Crowded Places","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","order":10,"questions":[{"question":"How do you feel when you are in a crowded place?","answer":"When I'm in a crowded place, I often feel overwhelmed and claustrophobic. It can be challenging to navigate through the crowd and find personal space.","ideas":["overwhelmed","claustrophobic","challenging to navigate","personal space"],"vocabulary":["crowded place","overwhelmed","claustrophobic","navigate","personal space"],"_id":{"$oid":"02264dde9ec09a2d81cae03d"},"order":1},{"question":"When was the last time you were in a crowded place?","answer":"The last time I was in a crowded place was during a music concert last month. The venue was packed with enthusiastic fans.","ideas":["music concert","last month","packed with enthusiastic fans"],"vocabulary":["crowded place","concert","enthusiastic","fans"],"_id":{"$oid":"710722030829d78ee6e00a70"},"order":2},{"question":"What places do you think are often crowded?","answer":"Places like shopping malls, tourist attractions, airports, and public transportation hubs are often crowded, especially during peak hours or holidays.","ideas":["shopping malls","tourist attractions","airports","public transportation hubs","peak hours","holidays"],"vocabulary":["crowded places","shopping malls","tourist attractions","airports","public transportation hubs","peak hours","holidays"],"_id":{"$oid":"c1b4bc99dd98aae9113f009f"},"order":3},{"question":"How often do you go to crowded places?","answer":"I try to avoid crowded places as much as possible, but sometimes it's unavoidable, especially when running errands or attending events.","ideas":["avoid as much as possible","unavoidable","running errands","attending events"],"vocabulary":["crowded places","avoid","unavoidable","errands","events"],"_id":{"$oid":"5adb74d0a3cc3a920b74a51e"},"order":4},{"question":"Do you like crowded places?","answer":"No, I prefer quieter and less crowded environments where I can relax and feel more comfortable.","ideas":["prefer quieter environments","less crowded","relax","feel more comfortable"],"vocabulary":["crowded places","quieter","comfortable"],"_id":{"$oid":"4d4296fec0da2a9fdef0f487"},"order":5}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"663ccd2d691ff22b0d1cc95d"},"name":"Being Bored","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","order":11,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"663ccd2d691ff22b0d1cc95d"},"question":"What things are boring to you?","answer":"Tasks that are repetitive or lack challenge tend to bore me. Also, long meetings or lectures without engaging content can be quite dull.","ideas":["repetitive tasks","lack of challenge","long meetings","lectures without engaging content"],"vocabulary":["boring things","repetitive","lack challenge","dull"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"663ccd2d691ff22b0d1cc95e"},"question":"What do you do when you feel bored?","answer":"When I feel bored, I try to engage in activities that I enjoy, such as reading, listening to music, or going for a walk. Sometimes, I also try to learn something new to stimulate my mind.","ideas":["reading","listening to music","going for a walk","learning something new"],"vocabulary":["feel bored","engage in activities","stimulate","mind"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"663ccd2d691ff22b0d1cc95f"},"question":"Do you ever get bored?","answer":"Yes, like everyone else, I experience boredom from time to time. It's a natural feeling that prompts us to seek new experiences or activities.","ideas":["experience boredom","natural feeling","seek new experiences","activities"],"vocabulary":["get bored","experience","prompts","activities"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"663ccd2d691ff22b0d1cc960"},"question":"Do you think school is boring?","answer":"School can be boring at times, especially if the material being taught is not engaging or if the teaching methods are outdated. However, there are also many opportunities for learning and growth in school.","ideas":["material not engaging","teaching methods outdated","opportunities for learning","growth in school"],"vocabulary":["school boring","material","engaging","outdated","learning","growth"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"663ccd2d691ff22b0d1cc961"},"question":"Do you feel more bored now than when you were young?","answer":"As I've gotten older, I've become better at finding ways to keep myself entertained, so I don't feel significantly more bored now than when I was young.","ideas":["better at finding ways","keep myself entertained","not significantly more bored"],"vocabulary":["feel bored","entertained","significantly"],"order":5}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"fc3c69a1ae6235a393b44348"},"name":"Singing","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","order":12,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"f6d1bac4f422d0b427eb481b"},"question":"Do you think singing can bring happiness to people?","answer":"Yes, singing can definitely bring happiness to people. It has the power to uplift spirits, relieve stress, and create a sense of joy and connection.","ideas":["uplift spirits","relieve stress","create joy and connection"],"vocabulary":["singing","happiness","uplift","relieve stress","joy","connection"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"7c3b8fdd8d9ec03ee38511ee"},"question":"Do you often sing?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy singing regularly. It's a hobby that brings me joy and allows me to express myself.","ideas":["enjoy singing","hobby","brings joy","express myself"],"vocabulary":["sing","joy","express"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"1b6896493e9dc0cfdea339c7"},"question":"When do you like to sing?","answer":"I like to sing when I'm alone at home, in the shower, or during karaoke nights with friends.","ideas":["alone at home","in the shower","during karaoke nights","with friends"],"vocabulary":["sing","alone","shower","karaoke","friends"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"c2db6eb1b5a09c4f97956f7c"},"question":"Is it difficult to sing well?","answer":"Singing well requires practice and training, but with dedication, anyone can improve their singing skills.","ideas":["practice","training","improve singing skills"],"vocabulary":["sing","difficult","practice","training","improve","skills"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"66dbaf8118e22caa162b2747"},"question":"Do you want to be a singer?","answer":"While I enjoy singing as a hobby, I don't aspire to be a professional singer. I prefer to keep it as a fun activity.","ideas":["enjoy singing","hobby","not aspire to be a professional singer","fun activity"],"vocabulary":["sing","aspirations","professional","fun"],"order":5},{"_id":{"$oid":"f7970af59fa6076a5e47afe7"},"question":"What kinds of music do you like to sing?","answer":"I enjoy singing a variety of music genres, including pop, rock, jazz, and classical. It depends on my mood and the occasion.","ideas":["variety of music genres","pop","rock","jazz","classical","depends on mood","occasion"],"vocabulary":["sing","music genres","pop","rock","jazz","classical","mood","occasion"],"order":6}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"7e2d7be12c5b30a463bf0ced"},"name":"Advertising","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","order":13,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"c916474c37fab2d3942b1ad7"},"question":"How do you feel about advertisements?","answer":"My feelings about advertisements vary. While some ads are informative or entertaining, others can be intrusive or annoying.","ideas":["informative ads","entertaining ads","intrusive ads","annoying ads"],"vocabulary":["advertisements","informative","entertaining","intrusive","annoying"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"4c660eefb99df81e8011a9ec"},"question":"Do you like advertisements?","answer":"It depends on the ad. Well-made advertisements that resonate with me can be enjoyable, but overly pushy or irrelevant ads are off-putting.","ideas":["well-made ads","enjoyable","pushy ads","irrelevant ads"],"vocabulary":["advertisements","enjoyable","pushy","irrelevant"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"b8b6ff2b59f3e6cada84a27f"},"question":"Do you like advertisements on TV?","answer":"I don't mind advertisements on TV as long as they're not excessive. However, I often use streaming services with ad-free options.","ideas":["advertisements on TV","excessive ads","streaming services","ad-free options"],"vocabulary":["TV advertisements","excessive","streaming","ad-free"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"e77e46ca5be2d8613ea36f66"},"question":"Is there much advertising in your country?","answer":"Yes, advertising is prevalent in my country. It's seen across various media platforms, including TV, radio, print, online, and outdoor billboards.","ideas":["prevalent advertising","media platforms","TV ads","radio ads","print ads","online ads","outdoor billboards"],"vocabulary":["advertising","prevalent","media","TV","radio","print","online","outdoor"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"1d1cf65e8ce10f75df17d856"},"question":"What are the different places where we see advertisements?","answer":"Advertisements can be found in various places such as TV, radio, newspapers, magazines, websites, social media, mobile apps, and public spaces.","ideas":["TV","radio","newspapers","magazines","websites","social media","mobile apps","public spaces"],"vocabulary":["advertisements","TV","radio","newspapers","magazines","websites","social media","mobile apps","public spaces"],"order":5},{"_id":{"$oid":"5f1640f98a808d67558c8cd1"},"question":"What advertising do you have in your country?","answer":"In my country, we have a wide range of advertising, including commercials on TV and radio, print ads in newspapers and magazines, online ads on websites and social media, as well as billboards and posters in public spaces.","ideas":["commercials on TV","commercials on radio","print ads","online ads","billboards","posters"],"vocabulary":["advertising","TV commercials","radio commercials","print","online","billboards","posters"],"order":6}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"d6a7e7295fe04dead2145d33"},"name":"Celebrities","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","order":14,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"dd43ae9a735137e6167e4b54"},"question":"Who is your favorite celebrity in your country?","answer":"My favorite celebrity in my country is [insert favorite celebrity name here]. I admire their talent, charisma, and positive influence on society.","ideas":["favorite celebrity","admire talent","admire charisma","positive influence"],"vocabulary":["celebrity","favorite","talent","charisma","positive influence"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"7a77ef662a10e0aa458c1e62"},"question":"Do you want to be a celebrity (or a pop star)?","answer":"While it might be exciting to be in the spotlight, I prefer a more private life. Being a celebrity comes with its own challenges and loss of privacy.","ideas":["exciting to be in the spotlight","prefer private life","challenges of being a celebrity","loss of privacy"],"vocabulary":["celebrity","pop star","spotlight","private life","challenges","privacy"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"44e98b3d8532a5bdd37a6b90"},"question":"Do you read news about celebrities?","answer":"Occasionally, I do read news about celebrities, especially if it's about their achievements or philanthropic efforts.","ideas":["read news about celebrities","achievements","philanthropic efforts"],"vocabulary":["news","celebrities","achievements","philanthropy"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"8630f099f603012dd954a03b"},"question":"Have you ever met celebrities face to face?","answer":"No, I've never had the opportunity to meet celebrities face to face. It would be an exciting experience if I ever do.","ideas":["met celebrities","face to face","exciting experience"],"vocabulary":["celebrities","face to face","exciting"],"order":4}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"ebd028d4f1e4797659d388e8"},"name":"Money","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","order":15,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"af5f870d868b7bf9731d22d1"},"question":"How can you save money?","answer":"There are various ways to save money, such as budgeting, cutting unnecessary expenses, setting financial goals, and investing wisely.","ideas":["budgeting","cutting expenses","setting financial goals","investing wisely"],"vocabulary":["save money","budgeting","expenses","financial goals","investing"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"d5394db607281d149114c8ed"},"question":"Why do people save money?","answer":"People save money to achieve financial security, fulfill future goals such as buying a house or retiring comfortably, and to have a safety net for unexpected expenses.","ideas":["achieve financial security","fulfill future goals","buying a house","retiring comfortably","safety net for unexpected expenses"],"vocabulary":["save money","financial security","future goals","buying","retiring","safety net","unexpected expenses"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"07c76525d8d09e65707283ea"},"question":"Did you save money when you were young?","answer":"Yes, I started saving money at a young age. It taught me the value of financial discipline and helped me build a habit of saving for the future.","ideas":["started saving money at a young age","value of financial discipline","building a habit of saving"],"vocabulary":["save money","young age","financial discipline","saving","habit"],"order":3}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"750fe7a7765ca78eb9629784"},"name":"Memory","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","order":16,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"b56fb4910dde2f0ee9fa1bb5"},"question":"How do you remember important things?","answer":"To remember important things, I use techniques such as repetition, association, visualization, and mnemonic devices.","ideas":["repetition","association","visualization","mnemonic devices"],"vocabulary":["remember","important things","techniques","repetition","association","visualization","mnemonic devices"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"4baea2c063c4b6226c84dba3"},"question":"Are you good at memorizing things?","answer":"Yes, I consider myself to be good at memorizing things. I find that practicing memory techniques helps me retain information more effectively.","ideas":["good at memorizing","practicing memory techniques","retain information effectively"],"vocabulary":["memorizing","memory techniques","retain information"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"c4a400af9f2722a53f2c87a8"},"question":"Have you ever forgotten something important?","answer":"Yes, I have forgotten something important before. It's a common human experience, but I try to learn from it and improve my memory skills.","ideas":["forgotten something important","common human experience","learn from it","improve memory skills"],"vocabulary":["forget","important","experience","learn","improve","memory skills"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"a9ba4169adb4057dd426a80d"},"question":"What do you need to remember in your daily life?","answer":"In my daily life, I need to remember appointments, tasks, deadlines, important dates, names, and phone numbers.","ideas":["appointments","tasks","deadlines","important dates","names","phone numbers"],"vocabulary":["remember","daily life","appointments","tasks","deadlines","important dates","names","phone numbers"],"order":4}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"6c9bb42fe30f0fa6cc70157a"},"name":"Video Games","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","order":17,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"75fa9cad0b6ed2d1b394df56"},"question":"Do you play video games?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy playing video games as a form of entertainment and relaxation.","ideas":["enjoy playing video games","entertainment","relaxation"],"vocabulary":["video games","enjoy","entertainment","relaxation"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"f26cc95390ecf9100f793e63"},"question":"Would you watch others play video games?","answer":"Yes, I would watch others play video games, especially if they're skilled or if it's a game I'm interested in but haven't played myself.","ideas":["watch others play video games","skilled players","games I'm interested in"],"vocabulary":["watch","play","video games","skilled","interested"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"1856827b933049ef578e234b"},"question":"Do you think people spend too much time playing video games?","answer":"While some people may spend excessive time playing video games, it ultimately depends on how they balance it with other responsibilities and activities.","ideas":["spend too much time","balance with other responsibilities","activities"],"vocabulary":["video games","time","balance","responsibilities","activities"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"4ca8021be04de8ba1814a1cc"},"question":"Do you prefer playing video games alone or with others?","answer":"It depends on the game and my mood. Sometimes I enjoy playing solo for a more immersive experience, while other times I prefer playing with friends for social interaction and teamwork.","ideas":["playing alone","immersive experience","playing with friends","social interaction","teamwork"],"vocabulary":["video games","alone","immersive","experience","friends","social interaction","teamwork"],"order":4}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"2f8f071498e0608845d13bc2"},"name":"T-shirts","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","order":18,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"09bdd787fc02089d9aaa08c4"},"question":"Would you buy t-shirts as souvenirs on vacation?","answer":"Yes, I often buy t-shirts as souvenirs on vacation. They're practical, easy to pack, and serve as a lasting reminder of the places I've visited.","ideas":["buy t-shirts as souvenirs","practical","easy to pack","lasting reminder"],"vocabulary":["t-shirts","souvenirs","practical","pack","reminder"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"d6015a3de554bdbd0aa91099"},"question":"Do you think older people who wear t-shirts are fashionable?","answer":"Fashion is subjective, and people of all ages can be fashionable in their own way, including wearing t-shirts. It's more about personal style and confidence.","ideas":["older people wearing t-shirts","fashionable","personal style","confidence"],"vocabulary":["older people","t-shirts","fashionable","style","confidence"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"c9556ada32ec3284f363f3ad"},"question":"Do you like t-shirts with pictures and prints?","answer":"Yes, I like t-shirts with pictures and prints. They add personality and style to my outfit, and I enjoy expressing myself through the designs.","ideas":["like t-shirts with pictures and prints","add personality","expressing myself"],"vocabulary":["t-shirts","pictures","prints","personality","expressing"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"9f099a27aea19315c6ab82f5"},"question":"Do you usually wear t-shirts?","answer":"Yes, I frequently wear t-shirts, especially during casual outings, sports activities, or when I want to feel comfortable.","ideas":["usually wear t-shirts","casual outings","sports activities","feel comfortable"],"vocabulary":["wear","t-shirts","casual","outings","sports","comfortable"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"1abc73510dc416fd7970d61c"},"question":"Do you like wearing t-shirts?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy wearing t-shirts. They're versatile, comfortable, and can be styled in various ways for different occasions.","ideas":["enjoy wearing t-shirts","versatile","comfortable","styled in various ways"],"vocabulary":["like","wearing","t-shirts","versatile","comfortable","styled"],"order":5}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"810c304be65bd0eb4cc4d2a9"},"name":"Outer Space","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","order":19,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"d3ea60c925fe2ca26b30e95a"},"question":"Are you interested in films about outer space and stars?","answer":"Yes, I'm fascinated by films about outer space and stars. They often inspire wonder and curiosity about the universe.","ideas":["interested in films about outer space and stars","fascinated","inspire wonder","curiosity about the universe"],"vocabulary":["films","outer space","stars","fascinated","inspire","wonder","curiosity","universe"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"535509716401d7fceb76c7f1"},"question":"Have you ever taken a course about stars?","answer":"No, I haven't taken a specific course about stars, but I've studied them as part of broader astronomy or physics courses.","ideas":["taken a course about stars","studied stars in broader courses","astronomy","physics"],"vocabulary":["course","stars","studied","astronomy","physics","broader"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"24ca601e9297948da62a6735"},"question":"Is it important to study stars?","answer":"Studying stars is crucial for understanding the universe, its origins, evolution, and our place within it. It helps unravel mysteries and advances our knowledge of astrophysics.","ideas":["important to study stars","understanding the universe","origins","evolution","our place within it","unravel mysteries","advances knowledge of astrophysics"],"vocabulary":["study","stars","important","understanding","universe","origins","evolution","place","mysteries","astrophysics"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"c277f84a18840f9095868f6c"},"question":"Do you like to watch the sky?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy watching the sky, especially during the night when I can observe the stars and contemplate the vastness of the universe.","ideas":["like to watch the sky","night sky","observe stars","contemplate vastness of the universe"],"vocabulary":["watch","sky","night","stars","observe","contemplate","vastness","universe"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"cb1ecbef4d1db77f37fb89bb"},"question":"What is the sky like at night in your hometown?","answer":"In my hometown, the night sky is usually clear, allowing for a stunning view of the stars. It's a peaceful and awe-inspiring sight.","ideas":["sky at night in hometown","clear sky","stunning view of stars","peaceful","awe-inspiring sight"],"vocabulary":["sky","night","hometown","clear","stars","stunning","peaceful","awe-inspiring"],"order":5},{"_id":{"$oid":"80e7d37aa59a3d262fbc15a4"},"question":"Do you like to watch stars?","answer":"Yes, I love watching stars. Their beauty and mystery never fail to captivate me.","ideas":["like to watch stars","love watching stars","beauty","mystery","captivate"],"vocabulary":["watch","stars","love","beauty","mystery","captivate"],"order":6},{"_id":{"$oid":"0e356de279a6ec7840373b4d"},"question":"What is your favorite star?","answer":"My favorite star is the Sun. It's essential for life on Earth and serves as the primary source of energy for our planet.","ideas":["favorite star","Sun","essential for life","primary source of energy"],"vocabulary":["favorite","star","Sun","essential","life","primary","energy"],"order":7}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"1c9dcdcca5d5d9e18979111e"},"name":"Numbers","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","order":20,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"86873a27f153063a2b74e741"},"question":"What is your favorite number?","answer":"As an AI, I don't have personal preferences, so I don't have a favorite number.","ideas":["favorite number","personal preferences"],"vocabulary":["favorite","number","personal preferences"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"a84896a65baf56191cd2d0a7"},"question":"Are you good at remembering phone numbers?","answer":"As an AI, I'm designed to process and store information efficiently, so I can remember phone numbers if needed.","ideas":["good at remembering phone numbers","designed to process and store information","remember phone numbers"],"vocabulary":["remembering","phone numbers","processing","storing","information"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"eba904b6ab08db4a9183075e"},"question":"Do you usually use numbers?","answer":"Yes, I frequently process and manipulate numerical data as part of my functions.","ideas":["usually use numbers","process numerical data","manipulate numbers"],"vocabulary":["use","numbers","process","numerical data","manipulate"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"99fa7823b0568cca619c43ad"},"question":"Are you good at math?","answer":"Yes, I'm proficient at performing mathematical calculations and solving equations.","ideas":["good at math","performing mathematical calculations","solving equations"],"vocabulary":["good","math","performing","mathematical calculations","solving","equations"],"order":4}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"1111b04b22bff28d44c26db5"},"name":"Keys","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","order":21,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"a5d7882a2c3749cd89200b3b"},"question":"Have you ever locked yourself out?","answer":"Yes, I've locked myself out before. It can be frustrating and inconvenient, but it's a common experience for many people.","ideas":["locked yourself out","frustrating","inconvenient","common experience"],"vocabulary":["locked out","frustrating","inconvenient","common","experience"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"21728828e516978763aa88a4"},"question":"Do you think it is a good idea to leave keys with a neighbor?","answer":"Leaving keys with a neighbor can be a convenient backup plan in case of emergencies or if you frequently misplace your keys. However, it's essential to trust your neighbor and ensure they can keep your keys secure.","ideas":["leave keys with neighbor","convenient backup plan","emergencies","trust neighbor","keep keys secure"],"vocabulary":["leave","keys","neighbor","convenient","backup plan","emergencies","trust","secure"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"f920bf2187e847ed24f68b45"},"question":"Have you ever lost keys?","answer":"Yes, I've lost keys before. It's a frustrating experience, especially if they're important or difficult to replace.","ideas":["lost keys","frustrating experience","important","difficult to replace"],"vocabulary":["lost","keys","frustrating","experience","important","difficult","replace"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"722a40426072a30abdca0ec6"},"question":"Do you always bring a lot of keys with you?","answer":"No, I usually carry only the necessary keys with me to avoid carrying excess weight and reduce the risk of losing them.","ideas":["always bring a lot of keys","carry necessary keys","avoid excess weight","reduce risk of losing"],"vocabulary":["always","bring","keys","carry","necessary","avoid","excess","weight","reduce","risk","losing"],"order":4}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"6108fc3e72ca94616b407c10"},"name":"Chocolate","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","order":22,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"6796315157a93adc6c22f47d"},"question":"How often do you eat chocolate?","answer":"I eat chocolate occasionally, usually as a treat or when I'm craving something sweet.","ideas":["eat chocolate occasionally","treat","craving something sweet"],"vocabulary":["eat","chocolate","occasionally","treat","craving","sweet"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"4a1be119c5e8f6807cc8e618"},"question":"Why do you think chocolate is popular all over the world?","answer":"Chocolate is popular worldwide due to its rich and indulgent taste, versatility in various desserts and confections, and its ability to evoke feelings of pleasure and comfort.","ideas":["chocolate is popular worldwide","rich and indulgent taste","versatility in desserts and confections","evoke feelings of pleasure and comfort"],"vocabulary":["popular","worldwide","rich","indulgent","taste","versatility","desserts","confections","evoke","feelings","pleasure","comfort"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"5fc8943027c70a2a28e81a82"},"question":"What is your favorite flavor of chocolate?","answer":"My favorite flavor of chocolate is dark chocolate. I enjoy its intense and slightly bitter taste.","ideas":["favorite flavor of chocolate","dark chocolate","intense taste","slightly bitter"],"vocabulary":["favorite","flavor","chocolate","dark chocolate","intense","taste","slightly","bitter"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"8c4f94d961f88be66bd53bde"},"question":"Do you like chocolate?","answer":"Yes, I love chocolate. It's a delightful treat that never fails to satisfy my sweet cravings.","ideas":["like chocolate","love chocolate","delightful treat","satisfy sweet cravings"],"vocabulary":["like","love","chocolate","delightful","treat","satisfy","sweet","cravings"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"4239e56ff279e0876c1d71ed"},"question":"Did you like chocolate when you were a child?","answer":"Yes, I've always enjoyed chocolate, even when I was a child. It's been a favorite treat of mine for as long as I can remember.","ideas":["like chocolate when you were a child","enjoyed chocolate","favorite treat"],"vocabulary":["like","chocolate","child","enjoyed","favorite","treat"],"order":5},{"_id":{"$oid":"7996c468bea7b836ba2c535a"},"question":"Did you give chocolate as a present to someone?","answer":"Yes, I've given chocolate as a present to friends and family on various occasions. It's a popular and well-received gift for many people.","ideas":["give chocolate as a present","friends and family","various occasions","popular gift","well-received"],"vocabulary":["give","chocolate","present","friends","family","occasions","popular","gift","well-received"],"order":6}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"f82a539d93336723bb8a8e7d"},"name":"Jewelry","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"09.05.2024","order":23,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"8ff2c4908e83b06cba32eeef"},"question":"Why do some people wear a piece of jewelry for a long time?","answer":"Some people wear a piece of jewelry for a long time because it holds sentimental value, reminds them of special moments or loved ones, or serves as a personal expression of style and identity.","ideas":["wear jewelry for a long time","sentimental value","special moments","loved ones","personal expression","style and identity"],"vocabulary":["wear","jewelry","long time","sentimental","value","special","moments","loved ones","personal","expression","style","identity"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"fd53599431bd9c95c0566225"},"question":"Do you like wearing jewelry?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy wearing jewelry as it adds an extra touch of elegance and personality to my outfit.","ideas":["like wearing jewelry","adds extra touch","elegance","personality","outfit"],"vocabulary":["like","wearing","jewelry","adds","extra","touch","elegance","personality","outfit"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"e7975a918eebd345ef9a145e"},"question":"What type of jewelry do you like to buy?","answer":"I prefer buying minimalist and versatile jewelry pieces that I can wear daily and easily match with different outfits.","ideas":["type of jewelry like to buy","minimalist","versatile","wear daily","match with different outfits"],"vocabulary":["type","jewelry","like","buy","minimalist","versatile","wear","daily","match","outfits"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"9cf573e30183d035f68aa5e8"},"question":"How often do you wear jewelry?","answer":"I wear jewelry almost every day, especially earrings and a simple necklace or bracelet.","ideas":["often wear jewelry","almost every day","earrings","simple necklace","bracelet"],"vocabulary":["often","wear","jewelry","almost","every day","earrings","simple","necklace","bracelet"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"d041a8d19b1f4a7be7ef7efb"},"question":"Do you wear a lot of jewelry?","answer":"No, I prefer to wear a few carefully chosen pieces of jewelry to avoid feeling overwhelmed or weighed down.","ideas":["wear a lot of jewelry","few carefully chosen pieces","avoid feeling overwhelmed","weighed down"],"vocabulary":["wear","lot","jewelry","few","carefully chosen","pieces","avoid","feeling","overwhelmed","weighed down"],"order":5},{"_id":{"$oid":"c62b25562c5a42fb00e59f31"},"question":"Have you ever sent someone jewelry as a gift?","answer":"Yes, I've sent jewelry as a gift to friends and family for special occasions like birthdays or anniversaries.","ideas":["sent jewelry as a gift","friends and family","special occasions","birthdays","anniversaries"],"vocabulary":["sent","jewelry","gift","friends","family","special","occasions","birthdays","anniversaries"],"order":6}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"783c2ffac31ce3aea573047e"},"name":"Sharing Things","author":"@user","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":24,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"9351a19fd67c7199ca0f2919"},"question":"Do you think kids like to share?","answer":"Yes, generally kids enjoy sharing, especially when they have positive experiences like trading toys or playing games together.","ideas":["kids like to share","positive experiences","trading toys","playing games together"],"vocabulary":["kids","like","share","positive","experiences","trading","toys","playing","games","together"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"af463d05586246b08b1a6de0"},"question":"Do you like to share things?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy sharing useful information or resources with others, as it fosters collaboration and mutual benefit.","ideas":["like to share","useful information","resources","fosters collaboration","mutual benefit"],"vocabulary":["like","share","useful","information","resources","fosters","collaboration","mutual","benefit"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"b50508155b565db810980267"},"question":"When you were a kid, did your parents encourage you to share things with others?","answer":"Yes, my parents always encouraged me to share my toys and snacks with friends, teaching me the importance of generosity and kindness.","ideas":["parents encourage to share","toys","snacks","friends","importance of generosity","importance of kindness"],"vocabulary":["parents","encourage","share","toys","snacks","friends","importance","generosity","kindness"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"bc2c3aad3fe9dcc12a3ec1b5"},"question":"Have you ever shared anything with anyone?","answer":"Yes, I've shared books, food, and even my time with friends and family, as sharing creates stronger bonds and enriches relationships.","ideas":["shared anything","books","food","time","friends and family","stronger bonds","enriches relationships"],"vocabulary":["shared","anything","books","food","time","friends","family","stronger","bonds","enriches","relationships"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"d0299ff55a9c14dc26b6338e"},"question":"What do you think of shared vehicles?","answer":"Shared vehicles, like carpooling or ride-sharing services, can be convenient and environmentally friendly alternatives to individual car ownership.","ideas":["shared vehicles","carpooling","ride-sharing services","convenient","environmentally friendly","alternatives","individual car ownership"],"vocabulary":["shared","vehicles","carpooling","ride-sharing","services","convenient","environmentally friendly","alternatives","individual","car","ownership"],"order":5},{"_id":{"$oid":"6a7207fbc4602bcc0906f66d"},"question":"Is there anything you don't want to share?","answer":"I prefer not to share personal belongings like my toothbrush or underwear, as they are hygienic items meant for individual use only.","ideas":["don't want to share","personal belongings","toothbrush","underwear","hygienic items","individual use"],"vocabulary":["don't","want","share","personal","belongings","toothbrush","underwear","hygienic","items","individual","use"],"order":6},{"_id":{"$oid":"d48129fcfeb4a6e88e090497"},"question":"What kind of things are not suitable for sharing?","answer":"Items like toothbrushes, underwear, and personal hygiene products are not suitable for sharing due to health and hygiene reasons.","ideas":["things not suitable for sharing","toothbrushes","underwear","personal hygiene products","health reasons","hygiene reasons"],"vocabulary":["things","not","suitable","sharing","toothbrushes","underwear","personal","hygiene","products","health","reasons"],"order":7}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"2872c150e1ccdc9a709ea81f"},"name":"Small Businesses","author":"@user","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":25,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"f2fb93c0a889a6b3ebdba49f"},"question":"Do you prefer buying things from big companies or from small businesses?","answer":"I usually prefer buying from small businesses because it supports local communities and often offers unique products or personalized services.","ideas":["prefer buying","big companies","small businesses","supporting small businesses","unique products","personalized services"],"vocabulary":["prefer","buying","big companies","small businesses","supporting","unique","products","personalized","services"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"778d4e4ba3dd573ffbf91f13"},"question":"Do you know many small businesses?","answer":"Yes, I'm familiar with several small businesses in my area, ranging from local cafes and boutiques to family-owned restaurants and specialty shops.","ideas":["know many small businesses","familiar with","local cafes","boutiques","family-owned restaurants","specialty shops"],"vocabulary":["know","many","small businesses","familiar","local","cafes","boutiques","family-owned","restaurants","specialty","shops"],"order":2}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"757d37632a9e431ee02582f7"},"name":"Staying at Home","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":26,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"50619207c90085ead521d68f"},"question":"What do you like to do at home?","answer":"At home, I enjoy activities like reading books, cooking new recipes, watching movies, and spending time with my family.","ideas":["like to do at home","reading books","cooking new recipes","watching movies","spending time with family"],"vocabulary":["like","do","home","reading","books","cooking","new recipes","watching","movies","spending time","family"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"5d26c63f320bb5e5b825a450"},"question":"How much time do you spend at home?","answer":"I spend most of my time at home, especially during weekdays. On average, I would say around 80% of my time is spent indoors.","ideas":["time spend at home","weekdays","most of time indoors"],"vocabulary":["time","spend","home","weekdays","most","indoors"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"7db9212de3323473fa370313"},"question":"Do you often stay at home? Why?","answer":"Yes, I often stay at home because it's my sanctuary. I feel most comfortable and relaxed in my own space. Plus, with the convenience of technology, I can accomplish many tasks without needing to go out.","ideas":["often stay at home","sanctuary","comfortable","relaxed","own space","convenience of technology","accomplish tasks"],"vocabulary":["often","stay","home","sanctuary","comfortable","relaxed","own","space","convenience","technology","accomplish","tasks"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"babb6364f8c2dc6f15ec9821"},"question":"Which do you prefer, staying at home or going outside?","answer":"I prefer staying at home most of the time. While going outside can be refreshing occasionally, I find solace and enjoyment in the comfort of my own home.","ideas":["prefer","staying at home","going outside","refreshing","solace","enjoyment","comfort of own home"],"vocabulary":["prefer","staying","home","going","outside","refreshing","solace","enjoyment","comfort","own","home"],"order":4}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"ec8b246575fe17b4ef1054ca"},"name":"Morning Routines","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":27,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"c88f3fb855d025e81f9da5c5"},"question":"Do you like to get up early?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy getting up early as it gives me a head start to the day and allows me to accomplish more tasks.","ideas":["like to get up early","head start to the day","accomplish more tasks"],"vocabulary":["like","get up","early","head start","day","accomplish","tasks"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"31e1add9ea2983ebf8d94994"},"question":"Is breakfast important?","answer":"Yes, breakfast is important as it provides the necessary nutrients and energy to kickstart the day. It also helps in improving focus and concentration.","ideas":["breakfast important","necessary nutrients","energy","kickstart the day","improving focus and concentration"],"vocabulary":["breakfast","important","necessary","nutrients","energy","kickstart","day","improving","focus","concentration"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"0ae2547c124058945a38b6f2"},"question":"When did you get up in the morning when you were a kid?","answer":"When I was a kid, I used to wake up early around 6 or 7 in the morning. It was usually around the time when my parents woke up.","ideas":["get up in the morning when a kid","6 or 7 in the morning","parents woke up"],"vocabulary":["get up","morning","kid","6","7","parents","woke up"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"4ecc589b1cc951939186e3a0"},"question":"What is your morning routine?","answer":"My morning routine usually involves waking up early, doing some light exercises or yoga, followed by having a nutritious breakfast. Then, I prepare for the day ahead by planning my tasks and goals.","ideas":["morning routine","waking up early","light exercises or yoga","nutritious breakfast","prepare for the day","planning tasks and goals"],"vocabulary":["morning","routine","waking up","early","light","exercises","yoga","nutritious","breakfast","prepare","day","planning","tasks","goals"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"b9c5c4653e6205ba52cbebf9"},"question":"Do you like the morning or the evening?","answer":"I prefer the morning as it signifies a fresh start and the potential for a productive day ahead.","ideas":["like the morning or evening","fresh start","productive day ahead"],"vocabulary":["like","morning","evening","fresh","start","productive","day","ahead"],"order":5},{"_id":{"$oid":"8fde4055105b695bf9c4d1dc"},"question":"What do you usually do in the evening?","answer":"In the evening, I often wind down by spending time with family, indulging in hobbies like reading or watching movies, and preparing for the next day.","ideas":["usually do in the evening","spending time with family","reading","watching movies","preparing for the next day"],"vocabulary":["usually","evening","spending time","family","reading","watching","movies","preparing","next day"],"order":6}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"318fb8429a5d8724faccc0ce"},"name":"Mobile Phones","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":28,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"577fbe1a283db62589b386c6"},"question":"What was your first mobile phone?","answer":"My first mobile phone was a Nokia 3310. It was a classic, sturdy device known for its durability and long battery life.","ideas":["first mobile phone","Nokia 3310","classic","sturdy","durability","long battery life"],"vocabulary":["first","mobile phone","Nokia 3310","classic","sturdy","durability","long","battery life"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"54dc1fd11658e9d8c4300426"},"question":"How often do you use your mobile phone?","answer":"I use my mobile phone frequently throughout the day for various tasks such as communication, entertainment, and productivity.","ideas":["often use mobile phone","frequently","tasks","communication","entertainment","productivity"],"vocabulary":["often","use","mobile phone","frequently","tasks","communication","entertainment","productivity"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"dbc45836b1326e367b7da0a1"},"question":"Do you use your mobile phone for texting or calls?","answer":"Yes, I use my mobile phone for both texting and calls. It serves as a convenient tool for staying connected with others.","ideas":["use mobile phone for texting or calls","texting","calls","convenient tool","staying connected with others"],"vocabulary":["use","mobile phone","texting","calls","convenient","tool","staying connected","others"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"2b877a6725ea6a6715c0fdca"},"question":"Can you describe your mobile phone?","answer":"My current mobile phone is a sleek smartphone with a large touchscreen display, high-resolution camera, and fast processor. It allows me to access a wide range of apps and services for both work and leisure.","ideas":["describe mobile phone","sleek smartphone","large touchscreen display","high-resolution camera","fast processor","access apps and services","work and leisure"],"vocabulary":["describe","mobile phone","sleek","smartphone","large","touchscreen","display","high-resolution","camera","fast","processor","access","apps","services","work","leisure"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"5bd406880e2dc9d865b6099a"},"question":"Will you buy a new mobile phone in the future?","answer":"Yes, I might consider buying a new mobile phone in the future to stay updated with the latest technology and features.","ideas":["buy new mobile phone in the future","consider","stay updated with latest technology and features"],"vocabulary":["buy","new","mobile phone","future","consider","stay updated","latest","technology","features"],"order":5},{"_id":{"$oid":"3f6c25c6ed16a987b39e550b"},"question":"How has your mobile phone changed your life?","answer":"My mobile phone has significantly changed my life by providing instant access to information, communication with loved ones regardless of distance, and enhancing productivity through various apps and tools.","ideas":["mobile phone changed life","instant access to information","communication with loved ones","enhancing productivity","apps and tools"],"vocabulary":["mobile phone","changed","life","instant","access","information","communication","loved ones","enhancing","productivity","apps","tools"],"order":6}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"83b07c4a93b930470f8b218c"},"name":"Fishing","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":29,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"8620380009012c11d4ad9855"},"question":"Have you ever been to a place where there are lots of fish around you?","answer":"Yes, I've been to places like lakes, rivers, and oceans where there are plenty of fish around. It's a serene experience being surrounded by nature's aquatic life.","ideas":["been to place with lots of fish","lakes","rivers","oceans","serene experience","surrounded by nature's aquatic life"],"vocabulary":["place","lots of fish","lakes","rivers","oceans","serene","experience","surrounded by","nature's","aquatic life"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"1ef314ebb822beab8d82a37f"},"question":"Is fishing popular in your country?","answer":"Yes, fishing is quite popular in my country. With its diverse water bodies and rich marine life, fishing has been a traditional activity enjoyed by many.","ideas":["fishing popular in country","diverse water bodies","rich marine life","traditional activity","enjoyed by many"],"vocabulary":["fishing","popular","country","diverse","water bodies","rich","marine life","traditional","activity","enjoyed by","many"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"ef362d40bef4a50de63f71b4"},"question":"Do you like eating fish?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy eating fish. It's not only delicious but also provides essential nutrients like omega-3 fatty acids, which are beneficial for health.","ideas":["like eating fish","delicious","essential nutrients","omega-3 fatty acids","beneficial for health"],"vocabulary":["like","eating","fish","delicious","essential","nutrients","omega-3 fatty acids","beneficial","health"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"a69ff1d77d2114f5ecb9f1cd"},"question":"Have you seen any movies with lots of fish?","answer":"Yes, I've seen movies like Finding Nemo and The Little Mermaid, which feature lots of fish. These movies often portray the underwater world in a colorful and fascinating way.","ideas":["seen movies with lots of fish","Finding Nemo","The Little Mermaid","underwater world","colorful","fascinating"],"vocabulary":["seen","movies","lots of fish","Finding Nemo","The Little Mermaid","underwater","world","colorful","fascinating"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"f5430f122ba7076eaa2c821c"},"question":"Why do people go fishing?","answer":"People go fishing for various reasons. Some do it as a recreational activity to relax and enjoy nature, while others fish for sustenance or as a sport to challenge their skills and patience.","ideas":["people go fishing","recreational activity","relax","enjoy nature","sustenance","sport","challenge skills","patience"],"vocabulary":["people","go","fishing","recreational","activity","relax","enjoy","nature","sustenance","sport","challenge","skills","patience"],"order":5}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"776605de53203822fc6a0923"},"name":"Robots","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":30,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"4feda90496692120dbf33b34"},"question":"Are robots important?","answer":"Absolutely, robots are incredibly important in today's world. They revolutionize industries, making processes more efficient and safer while also tackling tasks that are dangerous or monotonous for humans.","ideas":["robots important","revolutionize industries","efficient processes","safer","tackling dangerous tasks","tackling monotonous tasks"],"vocabulary":["robots","important","revolutionize","industries","efficient","processes","safer","tackling","dangerous","tasks","monotonous"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"02b5f18bbe2b8dfbb1416b36"},"question":"How can robots affect people's lives?","answer":"The impact of robots on people's lives is immense. They improve healthcare by aiding in surgeries and eldercare, boost productivity in workplaces, and can even serve as companions, especially for the elderly.","ideas":["robots affect people's lives","improve healthcare","aiding in surgeries","eldercare","boost productivity","serve as companions","elderly"],"vocabulary":["robots","affect","people's lives","improve","healthcare","aiding","surgeries","eldercare","boost","productivity","serve","companions","elderly"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"934919df07ec691d77aa64ab"},"question":"Are you interested in robots?","answer":"Absolutely, I find robots fascinating! The advancements in robotics are astounding, and I'm intrigued by how they continue to evolve and shape our world.","ideas":["interested in robots","advancements in robotics","evolve","shape our world"],"vocabulary":["interested","robots","advancements","robotics","evolve","shape","our world"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"30f638a3d99bf2b251bf0e0e"},"question":"Would you like robots to work at your home?","answer":"Absolutely, having robots at home would be fantastic! Imagine robots handling household chores, cooking meals, and ensuring security. It would make life so much easier and more convenient.","ideas":["like robots to work at home","handling household chores","cooking meals","ensuring security","easier","convenient"],"vocabulary":["like","robots","work","home","handling","household chores","cooking","meals","ensuring","security","easier","convenient"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"3fe0e5d2a8d0802b4830c532"},"question":"Do you want to take a car in which a robot is the driver?","answer":"Definitely! A car with a robot driver sounds like the future! It would be amazing to sit back, relax, and let the car handle the driving, especially considering the potential for increased safety and efficiency.","ideas":["take car with robot as driver","sit back","relax","handle the driving","increased safety","increased efficiency"],"vocabulary":["take","car","robot","driver","sit back","relax","handle","driving","increased","safety","efficiency"],"order":5}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"30c5abd12066776e5a296f09"},"name":"Geography","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":31,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"114089cb0102aed3598829d9"},"question":"Have you ever learned geography?","answer":"Yes, I have learned geography both in school and through personal exploration. It's fascinating to understand the Earth's diverse landscapes, climates, and cultures.","ideas":["learned geography","school","personal exploration","Earth's diverse landscapes","climates","cultures"],"vocabulary":["learned","geography","school","personal","exploration","Earth's","diverse","landscapes","climates","cultures"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"86a3e0734403929131bbd108"},"question":"Do you think geography is useful?","answer":"Absolutely, geography is incredibly useful! It helps us understand the world around us, from natural phenomena like earthquakes and weather patterns to human interactions and global economies.","ideas":["geography useful","understand world","natural phenomena","earthquakes","weather patterns","human interactions","global economies"],"vocabulary":["geography","useful","understand","world","natural","phenomena","earthquakes","weather","patterns","human","interactions","global","economies"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"c54f224e1dc9c26b0484abd1"},"question":"Do you like geography?","answer":"Yes, I find geography fascinating! Exploring different regions, learning about their unique features, and understanding how they interact with each other is both educational and enriching.","ideas":["like geography","fascinating","exploring different regions","unique features","interact with each other","educational","enriching"],"vocabulary":["like","geography","fascinating","exploring","different","regions","unique","features","interact","each other","educational","enriching"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"69732ad9a530943aa9654027"},"question":"Do you ever want to travel to a country because of its geographical location?","answer":"Absolutely! Geographical location can greatly influence the attractions and experiences a country offers. Whether it's the tropical beaches of the Caribbean, the majestic mountains of the Alps, or the cultural richness of countries along the Silk Road, geographical diversity often sparks my desire to travel.","ideas":["want to travel because of geographical location","influence attractions","experiences","tropical beaches","Caribbean","majestic mountains","Alps","cultural richness","Silk Road","geographical diversity"],"vocabulary":["want","travel","geographical location","influence","attractions","experiences","tropical","beaches","Caribbean","majestic","mountains","Alps","cultural","richness","Silk Road","geographical","diversity"],"order":4}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"bb67c733dd4c08f005191f72"},"name":"Gifts","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":32,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"6818d97d864a5e8297e9e9ab"},"question":"How do we choose gifts?","answer":"Choosing gifts often involves considering the recipient's interests, hobbies, and preferences. It's also essential to think about the occasion and the message you want to convey through the gift.","ideas":["choose gifts","recipient's interests","hobbies","preferences","occasion","message"],"vocabulary":["choose","gifts","recipient's","interests","hobbies","preferences","occasion","message"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"83ce9849424f2ebd71afd5e9"},"question":"What kind of gifts are popular in your country?","answer":"In my country, traditional gifts like chocolates, flowers, and personalized items are popular choices. Additionally, electronic gadgets, fashion accessories, and gourmet food baskets are also well-received.","ideas":["popular gifts in country","chocolates","flowers","personalized items","electronic gadgets","fashion accessories","gourmet food baskets"],"vocabulary":["popular","gifts","country","chocolates","flowers","personalized","items","electronic","gadgets","fashion","accessories","gourmet","food","baskets"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"543828d69d8207183456643f"},"question":"What's the best gift you ever received?","answer":"The best gift I ever received was a handwritten letter from a loved one, expressing their thoughts and feelings. It was deeply personal and meaningful, showing the effort and thoughtfulness put into it.","ideas":["best gift received","handwritten letter","loved one","expressing thoughts and feelings","personal","meaningful","effort","thoughtfulness"],"vocabulary":["best","gift","received","handwritten","letter","loved one","expressing","thoughts","feelings","personal","meaningful","effort","thoughtfulness"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"be10f576cea7ca40e94b3c46"},"question":"What do you give others as gifts?","answer":"I often give others gifts that are thoughtful and tailored to their interests. It could range from books, accessories, or experiences like concert tickets or spa vouchers.","ideas":["give others as gifts","thoughtful","tailored to interests","books","accessories","concert tickets","spa vouchers"],"vocabulary":["give","others","gifts","thoughtful","tailored","interests","books","accessories","concert","tickets","spa","vouchers"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"e8bf6541349fd513637c1651"},"question":"Do you like to give expensive gifts?","answer":"While I appreciate the sentiment behind expensive gifts, I believe the value of a gift lies more in its thoughtfulness and relevance to the recipient rather than its price tag.","ideas":["like to give expensive gifts","appreciate sentiment","value of a gift","thoughtfulness","relevance","recipient","price tag"],"vocabulary":["like","give","expensive","gifts","appreciate","sentiment","value","thoughtfulness","relevance","recipient","price","tag"],"order":5},{"_id":{"$oid":"316a5c54b046277ca921fbf8"},"question":"How often do you buy gifts for other people?","answer":"I try to buy gifts for others on special occasions like birthdays, holidays, or significant milestones. However, I also believe in spontaneous gestures of kindness, so I may buy gifts at other times as well.","ideas":["buy gifts for other people","special occasions","birthdays","holidays","significant milestones","spontaneous gestures of kindness"],"vocabulary":["buy","gifts","other","people","special","occasions","birthdays","holidays","significant","milestones","spontaneous","gestures","kindness"],"order":6},{"_id":{"$oid":"b55df35a1a349833371e891d"},"question":"Why do people give gifts?","answer":"People give gifts to express their love, appreciation, or gratitude towards others. It's also a way to celebrate special occasions, strengthen relationships, or simply bring joy to someone's day.","ideas":["people give gifts","express love","appreciation","gratitude","celebrate special occasions","strengthen relationships","bring joy"],"vocabulary":["people","give","gifts","express","love","appreciation","gratitude","celebrate","special","occasions","strengthen","relationships","bring","joy"],"order":7},{"_id":{"$oid":"3ec69efbea4e9e7ca659c9eb"},"question":"Have you ever received a gift which you didn't like?","answer":"Yes, I have received gifts that weren't quite my taste or suited my preferences. However, I always appreciate the thought and effort behind the gesture, regardless of whether the gift was to my liking.","ideas":["received gift didn't like","appreciate thought","appreciate effort","gesture","liking"],"vocabulary":["received","gift","didn't","like","appreciate","thought","effort","gesture","liking"],"order":8}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"2e72002be2db7ba5f5f91570"},"name":"Running","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":33,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"7fc1f04e6dbc9d3ebe94fbdc"},"question":"What do you think of running as a form of exercise?","answer":"Running is an excellent form of exercise that offers numerous physical and mental health benefits. It improves cardiovascular health, strengthens muscles, boosts mood, and can even enhance cognitive function.","ideas":["running as form of exercise","physical health benefits","mental health benefits","cardiovascular health","strengthens muscles","boosts mood","enhance cognitive function"],"vocabulary":["running","form","exercise","physical","health","benefits","mental","cardiovascular","strengthens","muscles","boosts","mood","enhance","cognitive","function"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"09858078ec3b0e83a15b006d"},"question":"Do you like running?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy running. It's not only a great way to stay fit and healthy but also allows me to clear my mind and relieve stress.","ideas":["like running","stay fit and healthy","clear mind","relieve stress"],"vocabulary":["like","running","stay","fit","healthy","clear","mind","relieve","stress"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"9ffc1712eb67546684350379"},"question":"Where do you run? Where do you go running?","answer":"I usually run in the park near my home or on designated running trails. Sometimes, I also enjoy running along scenic routes by the beach or through forested areas.","ideas":["where do you run","where do you go running","park near home","designated running trails","scenic routes","beach","forested areas"],"vocabulary":["run","where","go","running","park","near","home","designated","trails","scenic","routes","beach","forested","areas"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"5a2370a4d61c0f8404fb0227"},"question":"How often do you run?","answer":"I try to run several times a week to maintain my fitness level and enjoy the benefits of running regularly. However, the frequency may vary depending on my schedule and other commitments.","ideas":["often do you run","several times a week","maintain fitness level","enjoy benefits","regularly","frequency","schedule","commitments"],"vocabulary":["often","run","several","times","week","maintain","fitness","level","enjoy","benefits","regularly","frequency","schedule","commitments"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"798822f298a1fed8c95d954a"},"question":"Do you go running a lot?","answer":"Yes, I go running frequently. It's a regular part of my exercise routine, and I make sure to include it in my weekly schedule to stay active and healthy.","ideas":["go running a lot","frequently","regular part of exercise routine","include in weekly schedule","stay active","healthy"],"vocabulary":["go","running","lot","frequently","regular","part","exercise","routine","include","weekly","schedule","stay","active","healthy"],"order":5}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d500"},"name":"Films","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":34,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d501"},"question":"Do you like to watch films?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy watching films. They offer a great way to relax, be entertained, and explore different stories and perspectives.","ideas":["like to watch films","relax","be entertained","explore stories","explore perspectives"],"vocabulary":["like","watch","films","relax","entertained","explore","stories","perspectives"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d502"},"question":"What kinds of movies do you like best?","answer":"I enjoy a wide variety of movies, but I particularly like dramas, thrillers, and science fiction films. However, I'm always open to exploring different genres and discovering new favorites.","ideas":["kinds of movies you like best","dramas","thrillers","science fiction films","exploring different genres","discovering new favorites"],"vocabulary":["kinds","movies","like","best","dramas","thrillers","science fiction","films","exploring","different","genres","discovering","new","favorites"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d503"},"question":"How often do you go to a cinema to watch a movie?","answer":"I try to go to the cinema occasionally, especially when there's a highly anticipated movie release or when I want to experience a film on the big screen. However, I also enjoy watching movies at home.","ideas":["often go to cinema to watch movie","occasionally","highly anticipated movie release","experience film on big screen","watching movies at home"],"vocabulary":["often","go","cinema","watch","movie","occasionally","highly","anticipated","release","experience","film","big","screen","watching","home"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d504"},"question":"Did you usually go to the cinema when you were a kid?","answer":"Yes, going to the cinema was a fun and exciting activity when I was a kid. It was a special treat to see the latest movies on the big screen with friends or family.","ideas":["usually go to cinema when you were kid","fun","exciting activity","special treat","latest movies","big screen","friends","family"],"vocabulary":["usually","go","cinema","kid","fun","exciting","activity","special","treat","latest","movies","big","screen","friends","family"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d505"},"question":"What was the first film that you watched?","answer":"The first film I remember watching was a classic animated movie that captured my imagination and sparked my love for cinema at a young age.","ideas":["first film you watched","classic animated movie","captured imagination","sparked love for cinema","young age"],"vocabulary":["first","film","watched","classic","animated","movie","captured","imagination","sparked","love","cinema","young","age"],"order":5},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d506"},"question":"Do you like to watch movies alone or with your friends?","answer":"I enjoy both watching movies alone and with friends. Sometimes, I prefer the solitude and focus of watching a movie by myself, while other times, it's fun to share the experience and discuss the film with friends.","ideas":["like to watch movies alone or with friends","solitude","focus","share experience","discuss film"],"vocabulary":["like","watch","movies","alone","friends","solitude","focus","share","experience","discuss","film"],"order":6},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d507"},"question":"Do you prefer foreign films or films made in your country?","answer":"I appreciate both foreign films and those made in my country. Each offers a unique perspective and cultural insight, and I enjoy exploring stories from different parts of the world.","ideas":["prefer foreign films or films made in your country","appreciate both","unique perspective","cultural insight","exploring stories"],"vocabulary":["prefer","foreign","films","made","country","appreciate","both","unique","perspective","cultural","insight","exploring","stories"],"order":7}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d508"},"name":"Coffee","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":35,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d509"},"question":"Are tea and coffee popular in your country?","answer":"Yes, both tea and coffee are popular beverages in my country. They are enjoyed by people of all ages and are an integral part of daily life.","ideas":["tea and coffee popular","beverages","enjoyed by people","integral part of daily life"],"vocabulary":["tea","coffee","popular","beverages","enjoyed","people","integral","part","daily","life"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d50a"},"question":"Do people like tea or coffee nowadays?","answer":"Both tea and coffee remain popular choices nowadays. Preferences vary among individuals, with some preferring the bold flavor of coffee while others enjoy the soothing taste of tea.","ideas":["people like tea or coffee nowadays","preferences vary","bold flavor of coffee","soothing taste of tea"],"vocabulary":["people","like","tea","coffee","nowadays","preferences","vary","bold","flavor","soothing","taste"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d50b"},"question":"Do you prefer to drink tea or coffee?","answer":"I enjoy both tea and coffee, but if I had to choose, I would lean towards coffee. I appreciate its rich flavor and the caffeine boost it provides.","ideas":["prefer to drink tea or coffee","enjoy both","lean towards coffee","rich flavor","caffeine boost"],"vocabulary":["prefer","drink","tea","coffee","enjoy","both","lean","towards","rich","flavor","caffeine","boost"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d50c"},"question":"Do you like tea or coffee?","answer":"I enjoy both tea and coffee, as they offer unique flavors and aromas that I appreciate in different situations. Whether it's a warm cup of tea on a chilly evening or a revitalizing coffee in the morning, each has its charm.","ideas":["like tea or coffee","offer unique flavors","offer unique aromas","appreciate in different situations","warm cup of tea","revitalizing coffee"],"vocabulary":["like","tea","coffee","offer","unique","flavors","aromas","appreciate","different","situations","warm","cup","revitalizing"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d50d"},"question":"Do you often drink coffee and tea?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy drinking both coffee and tea regularly. They are my go-to beverages for various occasions, whether it's to kickstart my day or unwind in the evening.","ideas":["often drink coffee and tea","regularly","go-to beverages","kickstart day","unwind in the evening"],"vocabulary":["often","drink","coffee","tea","regularly","go-to","beverages","kickstart","day","unwind","evening"],"order":5}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d50e"},"name":"Musical Instrument","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":36,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d50f"},"question":"Have you ever learned to play a musical instrument?","answer":"Yes, I have learned to play a musical instrument. It was an enriching experience that not only taught me the beauty of music but also instilled discipline and patience.","ideas":["learned to play musical instrument","enriching experience","beauty of music","instilled discipline","instilled patience"],"vocabulary":["learned","play","musical instrument","enriching","experience","beauty","music","instilled","discipline","patience"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d510"},"question":"Is music an important subject at school in your country?","answer":"Yes, music is considered an important subject in schools in my country. It helps students develop creativity, cognitive skills, and appreciation for the arts.","ideas":["music important subject at school","develop creativity","develop cognitive skills","appreciation for the arts"],"vocabulary":["music","important","subject","school","develop","creativity","cognitive","skills","appreciation","arts"],"order":2}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d511"},"name":"Noise","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":37,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d512"},"question":"Do you mind noises?","answer":"It depends on the situation. While some noises don't bother me, others can be quite distracting and affect my concentration or mood.","ideas":["mind noises","bother","distracting","affect concentration","affect mood"],"vocabulary":["mind","noises","bother","distracting","affect","concentration","mood"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d513"},"question":"Do any noises bother you?","answer":"Yes, certain noises bother me, especially loud or repetitive ones. They can be disruptive and make it difficult to focus or relax.","ideas":["noises bother","loud","repetitive","disruptive","difficult to focus","difficult to relax"],"vocabulary":["noises","bother","loud","repetitive","disruptive","difficult","focus","relax"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d514"},"question":"Do you think there is too much noise in today's world?","answer":"Yes, I believe there is an abundance of noise in today's world, from traffic and construction noise to constant notifications from electronic devices. It's important to find moments of peace and quiet amidst the noise.","ideas":["too much noise in today's world","traffic noise","construction noise","constant notifications","electronic devices","find moments of peace","find moments of quiet"],"vocabulary":["much","noise","today's","world","traffic","construction","constant","notifications","electronic","devices","find","moments","peace","quiet"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d515"},"question":"What type of noise do you come across in your daily life?","answer":"In my daily life, I encounter various types of noise, including traffic noise, conversations, household appliances, and occasional construction or maintenance sounds.","ideas":["type of noise","traffic noise","conversations","household appliances","construction sounds","maintenance sounds"],"vocabulary":["type","noise","traffic","conversations","household","appliances","construction","sounds","maintenance"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d516"},"question":"Are there any sounds that you like?","answer":"Yes, I enjoy soothing sounds such as gentle rain, rustling leaves, or soft instrumental music. These sounds have a calming effect and help me relax.","ideas":["sounds you like","soothing sounds","gentle rain","rustling leaves","soft instrumental music","calming effect","help me relax"],"vocabulary":["sounds","like","soothing","gentle","rain","rustling","leaves","soft","instrumental","music","calming","effect","help","relax"],"order":5}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d517"},"name":"Helping Others","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":38,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d518"},"question":"Do you usually help people around you?","answer":"Yes, I strive to help people around me whenever I can. Whether it's lending a hand to neighbors, offering support to family members, or being there for friends in need, helping others brings fulfillment and strengthens bonds.","ideas":["usually help people around you","strive to help","lending a hand","offering support","being there for friends","bringing fulfillment","strengthening bonds"],"vocabulary":["usually","help","people","around","strive","lending","hand","offering","support","being","there","friends","bringing","fulfillment","strengthening","bonds"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d519"},"question":"How do you help people around you such as neighbors, family, and friends?","answer":"I help people around me in various ways. This includes simple acts of kindness like running errands for neighbors, offering a listening ear and emotional support to family members, and being available to assist friends with their needs or challenges.","ideas":["help people around you","running errands","offering a listening ear","emotional support","being available","assist friends","needs","challenges"],"vocabulary":["help","people","around","running","errands","offering","listening","ear","emotional","support","being","available","assist","friends","needs","challenges"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d51a"},"question":"Do your parents teach you how to help others?","answer":"Yes, my parents have instilled in me the value of helping others from a young age. They led by example and encouraged acts of kindness, empathy, and generosity towards those in need.","ideas":["parents teach you how to help others","instilled value","led by example","encouraged acts of kindness","empathy","generosity","those in need"],"vocabulary":["parents","teach","help","others","instilled","value","led","example","encouraged","acts","kindness","empathy","generosity","those","need"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d51b"},"question":"Did your parents help you a lot when you were young?","answer":"Yes, my parents were incredibly supportive and helped me a lot when I was young. They provided guidance, nurturance, and assistance in various aspects of my life, which helped shape who I am today.","ideas":["parents help you when you were young","supportive","provided guidance","nurturance","assistance","shaped who you are today"],"vocabulary":["parents","help","young","supportive","provided","guidance","nurturance","assistance","shaped","who","you","are","today"],"order":4}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d51c"},"name":"Maps","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":39,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d51d"},"question":"When was the first time you used a map?","answer":"I first used a map when I was a child, during a family road trip. It was fascinating to navigate through different routes and landmarks using the map, and it sparked my interest in exploring new places.","ideas":["first time used a map","child","family road trip","fascinating","navigate through routes","landmarks","sparked interest","exploring new places"],"vocabulary":["first","time","used","map","child","family","road","trip","fascinating","navigate","through","routes","landmarks","sparked","interest","exploring","new","places"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d51e"},"question":"How often do you use a map?","answer":"I use a map regularly, especially when traveling to unfamiliar places or planning outdoor activities. It's a handy tool for navigation and helps me find my way around with ease.","ideas":["often use a map","regularly","traveling to unfamiliar places","planning outdoor activities","handy tool","navigation","find way around","ease"],"vocabulary":["often","use","map","regularly","traveling","unfamiliar","places","planning","outdoor","activities","handy","tool","navigation","find","way","around","ease"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d51f"},"question":"Did you learn to use a map when you were a child?","answer":"Yes, I learned to use a map when I was a child, as it was considered an essential skill for navigating and understanding geographic locations. My parents taught me how to read maps, which proved valuable in my later adventures.","ideas":["learn to use a map when you were a child","essential skill","navigating","understanding geographic locations","parents taught me","read maps","valuable","later adventures"],"vocabulary":["learn","use","map","child","essential","skill","navigating","understanding","geographic","locations","parents","taught","me","read","maps","valuable","later","adventures"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d520"},"question":"Are you good at reading maps?","answer":"Yes, I consider myself proficient at reading maps. Over the years, I've honed my map-reading skills through practice and experience, which has helped me navigate various terrains effectively.","ideas":["good at reading maps","proficient","honed skills","practice","experience","navigate various terrains","effectively"],"vocabulary":["good","reading","maps","proficient","honed","skills","practice","experience","navigate","various","terrains","effectively"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d521"},"question":"Do you prefer electronic or paper maps?","answer":"While both electronic and paper maps have their advantages, I tend to prefer electronic maps for their convenience and real-time updates. They offer features like GPS navigation, which make them invaluable for modern travel.","ideas":["prefer electronic or paper maps","advantages","tend to prefer electronic maps","convenience","real-time updates","GPS navigation","invaluable","modern travel"],"vocabulary":["prefer","electronic","paper","maps","advantages","tend","convenience","real-time","updates","GPS","navigation","invaluable","modern","travel"],"order":5}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d522"},"name":"Chatting","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":40,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d523"},"question":"What do you like to talk about with your friends?","answer":"I enjoy discussing a wide range of topics with my friends, from hobbies and interests to current events, personal experiences, and future plans. Conversations often flow naturally, and it's enriching to share ideas and perspectives with each other.","ideas":["like to talk about with your friends","wide range of topics","hobbies","interests","current events","personal experiences","future plans","conversations flow naturally","enriching","share ideas","perspectives"],"vocabulary":["like","talk","friends","wide","range","topics","hobbies","interests","current","events","personal","experiences","future","plans","conversations","flow","naturally","enriching","share","ideas","perspectives"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d524"},"question":"Have your discussion topics changed since you were a child?","answer":"Yes, my discussion topics have evolved over the years. While as a child, my conversations might have revolved around toys, games, and school experiences, as I grew older, I began delving into more complex subjects like career aspirations, relationships, and societal issues.","ideas":["discussion topics changed since you were a child","evolved over the years","toys","games","school experiences","career aspirations","relationships","societal issues"],"vocabulary":["discussion","topics","changed","since","child","evolved","over","years","toys","games","school","experiences","career","aspirations","relationships","societal","issues"],"order":2}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d525"},"name":"Clothes","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":41,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d526"},"question":"What kind of clothes do you like to wear?","answer":"I like to wear comfortable and stylish clothes that reflect my personality and mood. This could range from casual jeans and t-shirts to more formal attire for special occasions.","ideas":["kind of clothes like to wear","comfortable","stylish","reflect personality","reflect mood","casual","jeans","t-shirts","formal attire","special occasions"],"vocabulary":["kind","clothes","like","wear","comfortable","stylish","reflect","personality","mood","casual","jeans","t-shirts","formal","attire","special","occasions"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d527"},"question":"What kind of clothes do you never wear?","answer":"I never wear clothes that are uncomfortable or don't suit my personal style. Additionally, I avoid clothes with offensive slogans or designs.","ideas":["kind of clothes never wear","uncomfortable","don't suit personal style","avoid","offensive slogans","offensive designs"],"vocabulary":["kind","clothes","never","wear","uncomfortable","suit","personal","style","avoid","offensive","slogans","designs"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d528"},"question":"Do you wear the same style of clothes on weekdays and weekends?","answer":"It depends on the occasion and my plans for the day. While I might opt for more casual attire on weekends, I dress according to the demands of the weekday, which could include business attire for work.","ideas":["wear same style of clothes on weekdays and weekends","occasion","plans for the day","casual attire","weekday demands","business attire","work"],"vocabulary":["wear","same","style","clothes","weekdays","weekends","occasion","plans","day","casual","attire","weekday","demands","business","work"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d529"},"question":"What color clothes do you like to wear?","answer":"I prefer wearing neutral colors like black, white, gray, and navy blue, as they are versatile and easy to mix and match with different outfits.","ideas":["color clothes like to wear","prefer","neutral colors","black","white","gray","navy blue","versatile","mix and match","different outfits"],"vocabulary":["color","clothes","like","wear","prefer","neutral","colors","black","white","gray","navy","blue","versatile","mix","match","different","outfits"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d52a"},"question":"Do people in your country like to wear bright colors?","answer":"Yes, people in my country often enjoy wearing bright colors, especially during festive occasions or in warmer seasons. Bright colors are seen as vibrant and celebratory.","ideas":["people in your country like to wear bright colors","often enjoy","festive occasions","warmer seasons","vibrant","celebratory"],"vocabulary":["people","country","like","wear","bright","colors","often","enjoy","festive","occasions","warmer","seasons","vibrant","celebratory"],"order":5},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d52b"},"question":"What are the differences between men and women's preference in color?","answer":"While preferences may vary individually, there are some general trends. Men often gravitate towards darker, muted colors and geometric patterns, while women may prefer brighter hues, floral prints, and a wider range of color choices.","ideas":["differences between men and women's preference in color","preferences may vary","general trends","men gravitate towards darker colors","muted colors","geometric patterns","women prefer brighter hues","floral prints","wider range of color choices"],"vocabulary":["differences","men","women's","preference","color","preferences","may","vary","individually","general","trends","gravitate","towards","darker","muted","geometric","patterns","brighter","hues","floral","prints","wider","range","choices"],"order":6}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d52c"},"name":"Transportation","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":42,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d52d"},"question":"What is the most popular means of transportation in your hometown?","answer":"In my hometown, the most popular means of transportation is by car, followed by public buses and motorcycles.","ideas":["most popular means of transportation in your hometown","car","public buses","motorcycles"],"vocabulary":["popular","means","transportation","hometown","car","public","buses","motorcycles"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d52e"},"question":"How do you go to work or school?","answer":"I usually go to work or school by car, as it offers convenience and flexibility in terms of timing and routes.","ideas":["go to work or school","car","convenience","flexibility","timing","routes"],"vocabulary":["go","work","school","car","convenience","flexibility","timing","routes"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d52f"},"question":"Will you use public transport more in the future?","answer":"Yes, I plan to use public transport more in the future, as it's environmentally friendly and can help reduce traffic congestion.","ideas":["use public transport more in the future","plan to use","environmentally friendly","reduce traffic congestion"],"vocabulary":["use","public","transport","more","future","plan","use","environmentally","friendly","reduce","traffic","congestion"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d530"},"question":"Are there any traffic problems in your area?","answer":"Yes, traffic problems are quite common in my area, especially during peak hours. Congestion, road accidents, and lack of efficient public transport contribute to these issues.","ideas":["traffic problems in your area","quite common","peak hours","congestion","road accidents","lack of efficient public transport","contribute"],"vocabulary":["traffic","problems","area","quite","common","peak","hours","congestion","road","accidents","lack","efficient","public","transport","contribute"],"order":4},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d531"},"question":"How would you improve transport in your town or area? How would you reduce traffic problems in your area? How do you think public transport could be improved?","answer":"To improve transport in my town, investing in better public transportation infrastructure and promoting alternative modes of transport like cycling and walking would be beneficial. Additionally, implementing traffic management strategies such as synchronized traffic lights and dedicated bus lanes can help reduce congestion. Improving the frequency and coverage of public transport routes, along with introducing modern amenities and technology like real-time tracking systems, can enhance the overall public transport experience.","ideas":["improve transport in your town or area","investing in better public transportation infrastructure","promoting alternative modes of transport","cycling","walking","implementing traffic management strategies","synchronized traffic lights","dedicated bus lanes","reduce congestion","improving frequency and coverage of public transport routes","introducing modern amenities","real-time tracking systems","enhance overall public transport experience"],"vocabulary":["improve","transport","town","area","investing","better","public","transportation","infrastructure","promoting","alternative","modes","cycling","walking","implementing","traffic","management","strategies","synchronized","lights","dedicated","bus","lanes","reduce","congestion","improving","frequency","coverage","routes","introducing","modern","amenities","real-time","tracking","systems","enhance","overall","experience"],"order":5}]},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d532"},"name":"Skills","author":"@nurmuhammad","lastUpdatedTime":"13.05.2024","order":43,"questions":[{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d533"},"question":"What are some skills you believe are important for personal development?","ideas":["important skills for personal development"],"vocabulary":["skills","believe","important","personal","development"],"order":1},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d534"},"question":"How do you prioritize acquiring new skills in your life?","ideas":["prioritize acquiring new skills","life"],"vocabulary":["prioritize","acquiring","new","skills","life"],"order":2},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d535"},"question":"Can you share an experience where learning a new skill significantly impacted your life?","ideas":["learning a new skill impacted your life","experience"],"vocabulary":["learning","new","skill","impacted","life","experience"],"order":3},{"_id":{"$oid":"6641cdc8435544100b61d536"},"question":"How do you stay motivated while mastering a challenging skill?","ideas":["stay motivated while mastering a challenging skill"],"vocabulary":["stay","motivated","mastering","challenging","skill"],"order":4}]}]